uesleisantoslima@gmail.com +55 79 996442111

www.uesleilima.com

www.linkedin.com/in/uesleilima in

Analyst and developer of information technology systems, with leadership skills and experience in web, mobile, embedded and service oriented systems, as also in financial and robust batch processing systems. Fast learner and easily adaptable. Enthusiast of agile software development process.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Banese Bank

02/2015 - Present Bank of Sergipe State Aracaju, Brazil

Tasks/Achievements

- System analyst and backend (JEE) developer of the bank core financial transaction authorization system
- Brought Integration testing automatization (IBM Rational Integration Tester expert) and process-structured code-review to the team
- Team substitute Scrum Master & Tech Leader / Member of the company Software Architecture Committee
- RESTful API 's designer and developer in both Java Spring and C# .NET platforms, also Spring Batch / Integration developer

Software Engineer

HPInc

02/2014 - 02/2015

Sao Paulo, Brazil

Hewlett-Packard's Brazil R&D Branch

- Tasks/Achievements
- Software Engineer of FutureSmart Multi-function Printer
- Frontend/backend development of the Web application interface. (C# / JavaScript)
- Web services maintenance and development
- Active participant of R&D discussion groups and development

Software Developer

Mikromatica Group

Sorocaba, Brazil

06/2014 - Present Tasks/Achievements

- Development of ASP.NET / WebForms / C# / Entity Framework application for Metrology management
- Microsoft Azure hosting and monitoring / SQL Azure

System Engineer

CESAR - Recife Advanced Systems and Research Center

02/2013 - 02/2014

Sorocaba, Brazil

Itabuna. Brazil

- Tasks/Achievements
- Software and systems engineering, Java (JSE/Swing) development, distributed systems architecture design
- Windows Mobile application entire life-cycle development (Conception, brainstorming, benchmarking and coding in XAML/C#)

Software Development Analyst

Intellisys Informatica Ltda

02/2012 - 02/2013

Tasks/Achievements

- CRM system Web application frontend/backend development and database maintenance
- Mobile application conception, analysis and development (Android)

SKILLS & COMPETENCES

Spring / Java Development .NET / C# Development RESTful Web APIs Design Scrum / Agile Enthusiast Software Architecture / Engineering Leadership Adaptability Resiliency

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science (03/2007 − 06/2012)

✓ University of Santa Cruz - UESC (Fully Government Paid)

Extended Studies in Development of Windows Applications (02/2013 - 08/2013) \Box

Recife Advanced Systems and Research Center - CESAR.EDU (HP Funded Scholarship)

Specialist in Software Architecture (03/2017 – Present) Pontifical Catholic University of Minas Gerais - PUC Minas

CERTIFICATES

Summit - Digital Payments And Distributed Technologies (03/2017 - 03/2017)

The challenges of using Blockchain in traditional banking system

Secure Software Development (11/2016 – 11/2016)

Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer - Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3 (01/2013 - Present)

Agile for IT Professionals (08/2012 – 08/2012)

Scrum and XP: Best practices for project management success. (03/2011 - 03/2011)

WEB Development with ASP.NET e C# (05/2010 – 05/2010)

ORGANIZATIONS

Computer Science Academic Center (04/2011 – 04/2012) President

INTERESTS

ΑI **Cloud Computing** IoT Software Architecture **REST API BPM** SOA Omni-Channel Backend **Distributed Systems** NoSQL Blockchain